Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
- Series II. 1900-1999
  - 1960-1969
    - Graham, David Lee, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Hall, Edward Gurden, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Hammond, David Baird, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 60)
      1939-2011
    - Hayden, David Winston, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Hayes, Kenneth Cronise, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Hertzendorf, Irving Issac, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 63)
      1941-1967
    - Higgins, Jerome Brion, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 64)
      1942-2011
    - Hill, Richard Albert, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 65)
      1939-1967
    - Hull, Bruce Lansing, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Jacobson, Robert Joseph, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Kahn, Donald Edward, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Kopec, John David, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Lamb, Lawrence Allan, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Lange, Richard Carl, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Lansing, William Edwin, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Legler, Robert James, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 73)
      1937-2008
    - Leslie, John Allen, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Loew, Franklin Martin, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 75)
      1939-2003
    - MacLeod, Ian Fullerton, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 76)
      1939-1972?
    - Meader, Charles Pennell, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Morse, James Royal, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Muddell, Clifford George, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Mullaney, Thomas Patrick, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Peddie, James Frederick, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Peddie, Linda Dixon Reeve, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Poggi, Louis Richard, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Proskine, Tyler Robinson, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Pulver, Robert Irwin, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Reiter, Martin Bruce, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Rind, Brian Irwin, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Savage, Edward Lee, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Sbarra, Jeremiah Nicholas, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Scherzo, Carmen Samuel [Albert], 1965 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Schoemann, Ralph Samuel, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Schwartz, Alan Elliot, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      1940-2008
    - Shapiro, Martin Paul, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Sharp, Ronald Kay, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Stokes, Mark Holmes, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Streett, John Walter, Jr., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Terry, John Melvin, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Thackaberry, Richard Gerwin, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Thoma, Richard Edward, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Thomas, Jim Dale, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      1941-1965
    - Tremper, Wayne Evan, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Veit, Hugo Paul, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Whitefield, John William, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Whitlock, Robert Henry, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Adams, Randolph Martin, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Alberding, Robert Milton, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Anderson, Glenn Arnold, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Andresen, John Edward, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Balogun, Peter, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      Class photo and negative; No Cornell DVM degree
    - Basciano, Peter Stephen, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Beck, Gary Fred, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Bushnell, Richard Warner, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      1935-1990
    - Cady, Errol John, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Cane, Gary Michael, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Christopher, Arthur William, Jr., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      1943-
    - Collins, Donald Ray, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Conway, Danice LaVerne, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Deitchman, Jonathan Peter, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Dwyer, John Alois, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Essex, Elizabeth Katherine Jordan, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Fernandez, Geoffrey LeRoy, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Fowles, Wayne Joel, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Garman, Robert Harvey, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Goldstein, Norman Harold, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Hansen, John Peter, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Harvey, Gale Howard, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Hayden, Margaret Ann Harris, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Herzig, Lee James, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Hess, Frederick Fleming, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - House, James Anthony, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Jones, Thomas Richard, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Kennett, Paul Donald, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - LaCroix, Jeffrey Alan, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Mach, Frederick Paul, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Moorhouse, Arnold Sydney, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Mountan, Paul Christopher, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Nelson, John Hjalmar, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 54)
      1941-2007
    - Newman, Harry Samuel, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Nilles, Bernard John, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Nowak, Edward Joseph, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Paeplow, John William, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Palin, Charles Herbert, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Pescod, Thomas Richard, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Platt, Kenneth Bradley, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Pollock, Melvin Gene, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Reese, David George, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Sancho, Victor, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 64)
      From British Guiana
    - Scribner, Peter Lowell, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Silverman, Jerald, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Smith, Ernest Karl, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 67)
      1943-2007
    - Tarr, Benjamin Dale, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 68)
      1941-2005
    - Thomas, Charles Leonard, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Ward, Jerrold Michael, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Witmer, John Ralph, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Wolf, Martin, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Wolfe, David August, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Youmans, Ray Sedric, Jr., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Zimber, Charles Paul, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Averill, Damon Rivers, Jr., 1967 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Beyer, George John, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Bliss, Ernest L., 1967 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Brown, Garrison Mack, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 79)
    - Burke, Jack, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Burroughs, Richard J., 1967 (Box 17, Folder 81)
    - Cary, Arnold Dean, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Ceglowski, Eugene Charles, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - Ceglowski, Jean Ruth Blume, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Cook, Roger Benham, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Dillmann, Christopher, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - Eskeli, Matthew William, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - Franzek, James Conrad, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Gardner, Michael H., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Garman, John L., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Gaskin, Jack M., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Goetchius, Paul F., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Gorra, Ferris G., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Hackathorn, Thomas Arthur, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Hart, Douglas W., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Hilt, John Wesley, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      1937-2013
    - Holden, Herbert Roger, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Ingraham, Allan John, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Frederick Wingate, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Kaplan, Joshua M., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Karpas, Dov, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Kaufmann, Gerard A., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Krakowsky, Jeffrey Norman, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Kubiak, Jan W., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Leahey, James M., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Leavitt, Edward Wilfred, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Martin, Edward Glenn, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Mathews, Leslie James, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - McMillan, Harry Thomas, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Meiczinger, James L., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      1943-2013
    - Miller, Lloyd E., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Missenis, John J., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      19??-2015
    - Myer, Carole Wendy, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - O'Keefe, Robert C., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Olin, Keith Merriam, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Parrish, David C., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Peddie, Donald Edward, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Powell, Josef M., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Rumsey, Leon D., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Schwartz, Victor J., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 33)
      1944-
    - Sequist, David B., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Snell, Glen D., Jr., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Stein, George, Jr., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 36)
      19??-2001
    - Stephenson, Robert J., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Walker, Jonathan Pearson, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Warriner, Wayne F., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Wilson, Terrence, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Witter, Alan F., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - White, Karl Karey, III, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Ackerman, Frederick Anthony, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Atlas, Harvey Stephen, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 44)
      1945-
    - Baum, Gary Mark, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Benyei, Curt Christian, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Bliss, DeGraff Everett, Jr., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Bogaard, Gerald John, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Bowen, Timothy Ayre, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Brody, Bernard Livingston, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Casadei, Peter Nino, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Conrad, Charles Roger, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Dalland, Edward Sigbjorn, Jr., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Feldman, Kenneth Donald, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Foster, David Ames, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Gallagher, Gregory William, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Gill, Harold Priestley, Jr., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Graycar, Barbara Frances [Kubiak, Barbara Frances Graycar], 1968 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Groskin, Robert Martin, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Hachten, Wayne Harold, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Hagan, David Kent, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Henes, Michael George, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Henry, Richard Peter, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Holmes, Crawford Cameron, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Kaufman, Charles Fred, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Keim, Guy Richard, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Kinsey, James David, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Kube, Thomas Smith, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Meyer, Alan Sidney, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Miller, Peter Morey, Jr., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Mueller, Robert Warren, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Nerenberg, John Allen, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Neveu, Peter Maurice, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Nolan, Paul Martin, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - North, John Arthur, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - O'Connor, Harry Patrick, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Parry, Enoch Wesley, II, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Pawlicki, James John, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Pomper, William Holloway, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Prowten, Allan Wainwright, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Putnam, Robert Norman, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Rafter, Maria Victoria, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Rathwell, Alan Clarke, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Redlus, Howard William, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Riehle, Henry Albert, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Schoonmaker, George Daniel, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Schuchman, Phillip Barry, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Scoville, David Farley, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Scudder, Keith Alden, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Seeber, Kenneth Paul, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 90)
      1943-2010
    - Silverstein, Gary Neil, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Steiner, John Victor, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Tremin, Paul Lewis, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Veley, William Allen, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Vogel, Alvin Josef, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Walker, David Johnson, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Wattie, Robert Thurston, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Weaver, Morris Greene, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Welsh, John Lawrence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - Wiest, Richard Dale, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - Zimmer, James Francis, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - Allen, William W., Jr., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - Beneke, George J., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 103)
      No class photo; negative only
    - Bilinski, Gerald, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - Brofee, Robert Dale, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    - Bushey, Clark Kenyon, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    - Casler, Michael J., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 107)
    - Clark, Edgar T., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 108)
    - Cousins, Oswald B., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 109)
    - Crafts, Gordon A., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 110)
    - Cutter, Arthur H., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 111)
      1943-2014
    - Darling, Larry E., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 112)
    - DeGroff, Leslie Edward, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 113)
    - DeLeo, Joseph R., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - Delius, Kenneth F., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - Dennis, Robert J., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 116)
    - Dennis, Timothy J., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 117)
    - Dungan, Paul B., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 118)
    - Dunnewold, Duane Donald, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 119)
    - Eisenhard, Carl L., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 120)
    - Fredericks, Richard W., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 121)
    - Giddings, Robert Fisk, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 122)
    - Gleason, John Lincoln, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    - Haddad, Joseph E., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    - Hayes, Raymond S., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Heffner, William A., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Holshuh, Harold Jacob, II, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Hopson, Gary R., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Howard, Courtland R., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Jefferson, David A., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Kaplan, Warren, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Karmin, Andrew, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Kelleway, Richard A., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Lamb, Bruce E., Jr., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Lerman, Mark, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Luger, Jay I., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - MacWilliams, Peter S., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Magnuson, Peter Alfred, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - McCauley, Alan David, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - McClure, James Gordon, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Miller, Alexander J., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      1946-
    - O'Connor, James R., Jr., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      1945-2012
    - Ojo, Yusuf, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Palka, Frank C., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Powell, Donald Carroll, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Roemmelt, John C., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Rogers, Dale Lewis, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Sadovsky, Roy, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Schmitt, Robert P., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Schneible, Paul G., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Schuchman, Stephen M., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Smiley, Paul Gerow, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Snyder, Milton Kirkwood, III, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Sprinkle, Ted A., Jr., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Taylor, Robert D., Jr., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Tompsett, James W., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Tumolo, Louis P., Jr., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Wood, Michael J., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Zemel, Robert M., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - 1970-1979
    - Averill, Eric W., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Blackmer, Paul Edwin, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Bradford, Clifford A., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 38)
      From Jamaica
    - Brunner, Michael Arthur, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Card, Richard Edwin, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Carlson, Kenneth A., Jr., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - DuBois, Edward J., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Durkac, Gabriel Thomas, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Ellis, Stephen K., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 44)
      1945-2013
      No class photo; incomplete contents
    - Epstein, Alan B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Ferber, Alan Richard, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Fernandes, Peter Thomas, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Glendening, James Robert, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Goldberg, Morton Arnold, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Gordon, Paul James, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Graham, Floyd H., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Gruhn, Ronald Fred, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Heissan, Joseph Anthony, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Hillis, Duane Frederick, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Hirsch, Leslie Stephen, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Holmes, George Ferguson, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Hutchins, Douglas B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Ireland, William Paul, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Kahn, Lawrence Alan, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Ketcham, Stewart Lyman, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - King, Stanley Eugene, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Kinnear, Paul Whitling, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Knapp, Joseph J., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - LaDue, Robert Charles, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Mauer, Lawrence Charles, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Melkonian, Gregory Jon, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Moak, Jeffrey S., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Morgan, James Thomas, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Moses, Jay D., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Otto, David Claflin, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Rosen, Ronald Jay, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Ross, David Alan, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Rowe, William Scott, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Schutz, John Paul, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Shephard, Valerie Jane [Syme, Valerie Jane Shephard], 1970 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Sherman, Arthur Harrison, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Smithling, Thomas Henry, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - St. Pierre, Stephen Joseph, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - Streams, Dale Calvin, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Stringfellow, David Alwood, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - Sykes, Gerald Kenneth, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Tillotson, Edward Louis, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Tischler, Steven Arnold, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 83)
      19??-2000
    - Tucker, Robert Dwight, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Vaughan, Timothy Reed, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - Wade, Donald Bruce, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - Wetherell, Linda Ann, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - Wing, Michael Andrew, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 88)
    - Woodworth, John Ralph, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 89)
    - Aldridge, John Paul, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 90)
    - Andre, Robert Louis, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 91)
    - Baldwin, Charles N., Jr., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 92)
    - Banser, John T., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 93)
    - Baum, Barry M., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 94)
    - Bellinger, Robert G., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 95)
    - Bender, William M., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 96)
    - Bernstein, Michael, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 97)
    - Beyel, David C., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 98)
    - Brinkmann, Theidire J., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 99)
    - Carlson, Jack H., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 100)
    - Clukey, Paul E., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 101)
    - Conolly, Richard Donald, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - Cummings, Clifford Glenn, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 103)
    - Davidson, Robert Randolph, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 104)
    - Ezeokoli, Daniel C., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 105)
    - Flinton, John H., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 106)
    - Freedman, Robert J., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 107)
    - Garrison, Fred Gregory, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 108)
    - Gelberg, Howard B., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 109)
    - George, Jeanne W., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 110)
    - George, Lisle Wesley, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 111)
    - Gingrich, John Andrew, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 112)
    - Goodnow, Lyle Calvin, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 113)
    - Hall, Brian E., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 114)
    - Herstein, Dennis M., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 115)
    - Kellner, Henry, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 116)
    - Kelly, William J., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 117)
    - Kemp, C. Edward, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 118)
    - Kingston, Richard S., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 119)
    - Klyza, James Philip, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 120)
    - Kraybill, Robert William, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 121)
    - Malnati, George A., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 122)
    - Manning, James L., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 123)
    - Mayne, Grant Jennings, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 124)
    - Meadow, Mark Richard, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 125)
    - Meisels, Lloyd Stuart, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 126)
    - Montagna, Charles R., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 127)
    - Orcutt, Robert Marshall, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 128)
    - Ouellette, John F., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 129)
    - Palmer, Foster K., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 130)
    - Price, Steven M., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 131)
    - Rebhun, William Charles, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 132)
      1947-1999
    - Reimels, Kenneth D., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 133)
    - Robinson, Donald L., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 134)
    - Saxton, Philip C., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 135)
    - Schimelman, Seymour J., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 136)
    - Shaw, Gary F., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 137)
    - Smith, Michael Scott, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 138)
    - Snyder, Randall P. A., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 139)
    - Sofarelli, Robert Joseph, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 140)
    - Surgeon, Thoulton W., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 141)
    - Vine, Martin Howard, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 142)
    - Vrooman, Dennis L., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 143)
    - White, Nathaniel A., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 144)
    - Wiesenfeld, Ira Robert, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 145)
    - Wiggers, Kent K., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 146)
    - Winkler, Kenneth I., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 147)
    - Wolski, Thomas R., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 148)
    - Wrightson, George D., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 149)
    - Young, Clark Montgomery, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 150)
    - Ahlers, Robert Alan, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 151)
    - Allen, Timothy A., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 152)
    - Almstrom, David H., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 153)
    - Armitstead, Thomas E., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 154)
    - Baker, George J., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 155)
    - Becker, Edward I., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 156)
    - Benjamin, Richard H., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 157)
    - Blessing, Calvin Edgar, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 158)
    - Bush, A. David, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 159)
    - Carlson, Paul K., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 160)
    - Cortesi, Paul J., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 161)
    - Dickey, Kenneth M., II, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 162)
    - Dirnberger, David Andrew, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 163)
    - Dougherty, Roderick B., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 164)
    - Eckerlin, Richard H., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 165)
    - Fisch, Harvey, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 166)
    - Foley, Robert H., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 167)
    - Friedland, Todd B., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 168)
    - Gluckman, Stuart I., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 169)
    - Goldstein, Damon R., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 170)
    - Guild, Phillip V., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 171)
    - Hahn, Edward G., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 172)
    - Harris, Alan M., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 173)
    - Higgins, William P., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 174)
    - Horowitz, Martin S., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 175)
    - Howard, David James, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 176)
    - Johnson, Robert H., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 177)
    - Kazmierczak, John Julian, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 178)
    - Kerbin, Priscilla L., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 179)
    - Kessler, Matthew J., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 180)
    - Knight, Walter Franklin, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 181)
    - Krasuski, Frank A., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 182)
    - Krepp, James C., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 183)
    - Kross, Steven H., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 184)
    - Letchworth, Geoffrey J., III, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 185)
    - McGee, David L., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - McMillen, Thomas B., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Miller, Daniel K., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Miller, Jeffrey Richard, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Moss, Kenneth J., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Pease, Clinton L., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Pettee, James Thomas, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Pijanowski, Gerald J., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Pinckney, John Ederle, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Rand, James Albert, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Reeve, Laurence H., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Mary Caroline Cole, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Speciale, John, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Tangredi, Basil P., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 14)